Why do I take torriso?
To griso I can make pancakes
to I can share my handiwork.
Tryo I can play dress up. Triso is a
once daily pill that's a targeted
therapy approved for adults with non
small cell lung cancer and certain eGFR
mutations when lung cancer has spread to
other parts of the body. Triso helped
patients live longer.
[Music]
Serious side effects that may lead to
death include severe lung problems,
heart problems, including heart failure,
and blood and bone marrow problems.
Other serious side effects can include
eye and skin problems, and inflammation
of the blood vessels in your skin. Tell
your doctor right away if you have
trouble breathing, shortness of breath,
tiredness, weakness, cough, fever or
infection, pounding or racing heart,
swelling of your ankles or feet,
dizziness, or any eye problems. Severe
blistering and peeling of the skin,
purple spots, skin redness, large hives
that last more than one day, or easy
bruising or bleeding that won't stop.
These are not all the possible side
effects. Tryo can harm your unborn baby.
Ask your doctor about pregnancy,
breastfeeding, and birth control. to
Griso I can live longer
to Griso I can ask for the number one
prescribed medicine for EGFR positive
metastatic NSLC.
Ask your doctor if Triso is right for
you.
[Music]